{
    "grades": [
        {
            "grade": 2,
            "questions": [
                {
                    "difficulty": "easy",
                    "items": [
                        {"question": "5 - 3", "choices": ["1", "2", "3", "4"], "answer": "2"},
                        {"question": "2/6 & 4/6", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": "<"},
                        {"question": "1cm & 1m", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": "<"},
                        {"question": "9 - 0", "choices": ["7", "8", "9", "10"], "answer": "9"},
                        {"question": "1/3 & 2/3", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": "<"},
                        {"question": "1m & 100cm", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": "="},
                        {"question": "22 - 12", "choices": ["8", "10", "12", "14"], "answer": "10"},
                        {"question": "5/8 & 3/8", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": ">"},
                        {"question": "5cm & 2m", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": "<"},
                        {"question": "8 - 5", "choices": ["2", "3", "4", "5"], "answer": "3"},
                        {"question": "1/4 & 1/4", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": "="},
                        {"question": "6m & 25cm", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": ">"},
                        {"question": "10 - 3", "choices": ["5", "6", "7", "8"], "answer": "7"},
                        {"question": "11/12 & 5/12", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": ">"},
                        {"question": "2m & 30cm", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": ">"},
                        {"question": "15 - 10", "choices": ["3", "4", "5", "6"], "answer": "5"},
                        {"question": "2/5 & 4/5", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": "<"},
                        {"question": "45cm & 36m", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": "<"},
                        {"question": "17 - 17", "choices": ["-1", "0", "1", "2"], "answer": "0"},
                        {"question": "7/10 & 3/10", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": ">"}
                    ]
                }      ,
                {
                    "difficulty": "medium",
                    "items": [
                        {"question": "55 - 8", "choices": ["46", "47", "48", "49"], "answer": "47"},
                        {"question": "6/12 & 2/12", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": ">"},
                        {"question": "29cm & 25cm", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": ">"},
                        {"question": "48 - 15", "choices": ["32", "33", "34", "35"], "answer": "33"},
                        {"question": "5/15 & 10/15", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": "<"},
                        {"question": "3m & 3cm", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": ">"},
                        {"question": "35 - 10", "choices": ["24", "25", "26", "27"], "answer": "25"},
                        {"question": "1/10 & 3/10", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": "<"},
                        {"question": "300cm & 3m", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": "="},
                        {"question": "88 - 25", "choices": ["61", "62", "63", "64"], "answer": "63"},
                        {"question": "4/12 & 8/12", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": "<"},
                        {"question": "7m & 7cm", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": ">"},
                        {"question": "73 - 35", "choices": ["37", "38", "39", "40"], "answer": "38"},
                        {"question": "3/8 & 1/8", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": ">"},
                        {"question": "300cm & 30m", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": "<"},
                        {"question": "25 - 5", "choices": ["19", "20", "21", "22"], "answer": "20"},
                        {"question": "4/16 & 8/16", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": "<"},
                        {"question": "2m & 350cm", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": "<"},
                        {"question": "66 - 26", "choices": ["39", "40", "41", "42"], "answer": "40"},
                        {"question": "7/18 & 7/18", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": "="}
                    ]
                },
                {
                    "difficulty": "hard",
                    "items": [
                        {"question": "157 - 58", "choices": ["98", "99", "100", "101"], "answer": "99"},
                        {"question": "7/19 & 6/19", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": ">"},
                        {"question": ".5m & 25cm", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": ">"},
                        {"question": "551 - 370", "choices": ["180", "181", "182", "183"], "answer": "181"},
                        {"question": "13/25 & 5/25", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": ">"},
                        {"question": ".3m & 3m", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": "<"},
                        {"question": "661 - 554", "choices": ["106", "107", "108", "109"], "answer": "107"},
                        {"question": "9/22 & 9/22", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": "="},
                        {"question": "400cm & 200m", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": "<"},
                        {"question": "240 - 73", "choices": ["166", "167", "168", "169"], "answer": "167"},
                        {"question": "5/29 & 16/29", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": "<"},
                        {"question": "42m & 15cm", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": ">"},
                        {"question": "202 - 98", "choices": ["103", "104", "105", "106"], "answer": "104"},
                        {"question": "7/17 & 9/17", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": "<"},
                        {"question": "35cm & 520cm", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": "<"},
                        {"question": "326 - 159", "choices": ["166", "167", "168", "169"], "answer": "167"},
                        {"question": "15/26 & 9/26", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": ">"},
                        {"question": ".5m & 50cm", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": "="},
                        {"question": "268 - 65", "choices": ["202", "203", "204", "205"], "answer": "203"},
                        {"question": "250cm & 1.5m", "choices": ["<", ">", "="], "answer": ">"}
                    ]
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}

